American Vaudeville Museum collection, 1850s-2007 (bulk 1910s-1940s)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series XXVIII: Media, ca. 2000-2007, .75 linear foot
  - 3-1/4 inch disks and zip drives
    - Rooney family - Pat Rooney, clog dancing; Pat Rooney and Marion Bent; Pat Rooney Sr. and Jr. (3 disks of images) (Box 71, Folder 13)
    - The Royal Rockets - text by Nick Retson (disk) and images (zip drive) (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Series XXIX: Commemoratives, undated, .25 linear foot
  This series comprises a ribbon, two pins, and an engraved spoon related to vaudeville.
  - Spoon - "Proctor's", engraved with floral design (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Pin - Orpheum Circuit "100th Anniversary of Vaudeville" Greater Season (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Pin - Vaudeville's 100th Anniversary Greater Keith-Albee Season (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Ribbon - Assistance League Vaudeville Flower Committee (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Series XXX: Hippodrome Theatre Actors' Accessories, ca. 1910s, 10.75 linear feet
  This series contains wigs, beards and other assorted hair pieces and dressings, wig blocks, numerous curling irons and cork for black-face make-up, used at the Hippodrome Theatre in New York during the World War I era.
  - Costume accessories and aids (Box 73)
    Aluminum pan for cork
    Bottle of hair oil
    Corks (7)
    Curling irons (7)
    Jars of burnt cork (2)
    Metal picks (2)
    Wig blocks (2)
  - Costume accessories and wigs (Box 74)
    - Black knit skullcap
    - Box of small costume accessories
      Black gauze
      Corncob pipe
      Eyeglasses
      Hairpins
      Floral pins
      Lip rouge
      Mascara
      Needle threader
      Pince-nez and case
    - Collars, starched (4)
    - Wigs
  - Wigs (Box 75-82)
- Series XXXI: Performance Costumes, undated, 2.75 linear feet
  This series comprises seven costumes and two wigs, of unspecified provenance.
  - Coster costume (for singing/dancing stage portrayal of a Cockney fruit peddler), Includes trousers, vest, jacket, hat and spats. Extra loose buttons were attached at the time of archive processing. (Box 83)
  - Other performance costumes (Box 84)
    Oriental style dress, in blue, gold and green patterned silk
    Black velvet coat
    Black and cream silk dress with bead trim
    Black pleated two-piece dress
    Shoulderless gown of gold-threaded fabric with tucked bodice, bead and embroidery decoration, and beaded fringe along hem
    Straw-colored two-piece linen dress with tatted trim
    Red comic wigs (2)
- Series XXXII: LP Record Collection, American Vaudeville Museum, 11.3 linear feet (Box 85-107)
  - Subseries 1: LP records: Blues, Revue, Jazz, and Cabaret - Solo Singers
    This series consists of record albums documenting 155 solo singers, mostly women. The number of LPs by each singer is given in parentheses.
    - A - Be (Box 85)
      David Allyn (1)
      Lorez Alexandria (3)
      Mose Allison (1)
      Ernestine Anderson (3)
      Ivie Anderson/other side Lena Horne (1)
      Andrews Sisters (4)
      Gene Austin (1)
      Charles Arznavour(3)
      Mildred Bailey (4)
      Pearl Bailey (1)
      Belle Baker /other side Sophie Tucker (1)
      Chet Baker (1)
      Josephine Baker (1)
      Sweet Emma Barrett (1)
      Dee Bell (1)
      Tony Bennett (2)
    - Bo - Cr (Box 86)
      Boswell Sisters (1)
      Connee Boswell (1)
      Fanny Brice (1)
      Stella Brooks (1)
      Ruth Brown (1)
      Wini Brown (1)
      Cab Calloway (1)
      Larry Carr (2)
      Betty Carter (3)
      Ray Charles (3)
      Jeannie (& Jimmy) Cheatham (1)
      June Christy (3)
      Steve Clayton & Marlene Ver Planck (1)
      Rosemary Clooney (2)
      Charles Cochran (1)
      Chris Connor (4)
      Barbara Cook (3)
      Ida Cox (3)
      Bing Crosby (3)
    - Da - Fa (Box 87)
      Dardanelle (13), some autographed
      Blossom Dearie (8)
      Marlene Dietrich (1)
      Bob Dorough (2)
      Anita Ellis (1)
      Cass Elliot (with Tim Rose & Jim Hendricks) as the Big Three (1)
      Ruth Etting (4)
      Alice Faye (2)
      Frances Faye (6) incl. Porgy & Bess with Mel Tormé
    - Fi - Hol (Box 88)
      Ella Fitzgerald (11)
      Roberta Flack (3)
      Aretha Franklin (2)
      Stan Freeman (1)
      Dave Frishberg (1)
      Helen Grayco (1)
      Lil Green (2)
      Adelaide Hall (1)
      Nancy Harrow (2)
      Johnny Hartman (3), one with John Coltrane
      Dick Haymes (1)
      Jon Hendricks (2)
      Al Hibbler (1)
      Billie Holiday (7)
      Libby Holman (1)
    - Hop - King (B.B) (Box 89)
      Linda Hopkins (1)
      Helen Humes (9)
      Alberta Hunter (3), one with Lovie Austin
      Jackie & Roy ( Jackie Cain and Roy Kral) (3)
      Mahalia Jackson (2)
      Al Jarreau (2)
      Eddie Jefferson (1)
      Lonnie Johnson (7), one with Victoria Spivey
      Al Jolson (3)
      Etta Jones (1)
      Greta Keller (2)
      B.B. King (1)
    - King (Morgana) - Lee (Ada) (Box 90)
      Morgana King (4)
      Teddi King (3)
      Eartha Kitt (1)
      Irene Kral (2)
      Gene Krupa (1)
      Cleo Laine (9)
      Lambert, Hendricks & Ross (1), one with Joe Williams & Count Basie
      Gertrude Lawrence (1)
      Barbara Lea (11)
      Ada Lee (1)
    - Lee (Peggy) - McRae (Box 91)
      Peggy Lee (5)
      Carol Leigh (1)
      Lotte Lenya (4)
      Katherine Handy Lewis (1)
      Abbey Lincoln (1)
      Dorothy Loudon (1)
      Vera Lynn (3)
      Gloria Lynne (1)
      Manhattan Transfer (2)
      Big Maybelle (1)
      Carmen McRae (19)
    - McRae - O'Day (Box 92)
      Carmen McRae
      Mabel Mercer (5)
      Helen Merrill (3)
      Tony Middleton (1), with Ellis Larkins
      Mills Brothers (1), with Count Basie
      Ada Moore (1)
      Helen Morgan (1)
      Lee Morse (1)
      Anne Marie Moss (2), one with Jackie Paris
      Gertrude Niessen /other side Josephine Baker (1)
      Helen O'Connell (4)
      Anita O'Day (19), some autographed
    - O'Day - Shan (Box 93)
      Anita O'Day
      Bernadette Peters (2)
      Esther Phillips (1)
      King Pleasure (1)
      Maria Postell (1)
      Josephine Premice (1)
      Arthur Prysock (1,) with Count Basie
      Ma Rainey (4)
      Martha Raye (1)
      Bertice Reading (1)
      Della Reese (1)
      Harry Richman / other side Sophie Tucker (1)
      Betty Roche (1)
      Eileen Rodgers (1)
      Annie Ross (1)
      Jimmy Rushing (2)
      Hugh Shannon (1)
    - Shay - Smith (Bessie) (Box 94)
      Dorothy Shay (1)
      Daryl Sherman (2)
      Bobby Short (4)
      Nina Simone (3)
      Frank Sinatra (1)
      Carol Sloane (2)
      Bessie Smith (13)
    - Smith (Carrie) - To (Box 95)
      Carrie Smith (3)
      Keely Smith (1)
      Valaida Snow (1)
      Victoria Spivey (3)
      Jo Stafford (2)
      Dakota Staton (1)
      Kay Starr (2), one with Erroll Garner
      Joan Steele (2)
      Maxine Sullivan (10), some autographed
      Sweet Honey in the Rock (1)
      Sylvia Syms (4)
      Mel Tormé (5)
    - Tr - Wash (Box 96)
      Thom Troy (1)
      Sophie Tucker (2)
      Big Joe Turner (2)
      Sarah Vaughan (13)
      Frederica Von Stade (1)
      Sippie Wallace (2)
      Fats Waller (3)
      Clara Ward (1)
      Dinah Washington (6)
    - Wat - Whit (Box 97)
      Ethel Waters (17)
      Elisabeth Welch (2)
      Mae West (10)
      Georgia White (1)
      Margaret Whiting (5), one autographed
    - Whit - Whyte (Box 98)
      Margaret Whiting
      Lee Wiley (19)
      Marion Williams (7)
      Marie Wilson (1)
      Jimmy Witherspoon (2)
      Ronnie Whyte (1)
  - Subseries 2: LP records: Blues, Revue, Jazz, and Cabaret - Compilations
    This series consists of compilations, mostly of songs by women singers. There are multiple singers on 18 blues or jazz LPs - many of them on the Rosetta label. The number in parentheses is the number of LPs on which each of the listed 160 singers performs. No number in parentheses means the singer performs on only one compilation LP.
    - Almost Like Being in Love – Women's Railroad Blues (Box 99)
      Ora Alexandra
      Annisteen Allen
      Ivie Anderson
      Andrews Sisters
      Nancy Andrews
      Lil Armstrong (5)
      Jim Bailey
      Mildred Bailey (3)
      Kaye Ballard
      Blue Lou Barker (3)
      Gladys Bentley (3)
      Lucille Bogan (3)
      Hadda Brooks (2)
      Ada Brown
      Bessie Brown
      Cleo Brown (2)
      Sweet Georgia Brown
      Butterbeans & Susie ( Jodie Edwards & Susie Edwards), 3 duets/one Susie solo (4)
      Cab Calloway (2)
      Una Mae Carlisle (2)
      Christine Chatman
      June Christy
      Rosemary Clooney
      Marilyn Cooper
      Martha Copeland (4)
      Ida Cox (4)
      Dardanelle
      Blossom Dearie (4)
      Gloria De Haven
      Johnny Desmond
      Phyllis Diller
      Mary Dixon (2)
      Tina Dixon
      Dorothy Donegan
      Warde Donovan
      Arizona Dranes
      Bernice Edwards (2)
      Edward Earle
      Ella Fitzgerald (4)
      Rhonda Fleming
      Bea Foote (2)
      Helen Forrest
      Mozelle France & Mae Hopkins ( Bandana Girls)
      Jane Froman
      Judy Garland
      Cleo Gibson (2)
      Hermione Gingold
      Lillian Glinn
      Fannie Mae Goosby
      Eydie Gorme
      Lil Green
      Harlem Hannah ( Peggy English)
      Rosa Henderson (2)
      Lawrence Harvey
      Bertha Chippie Hill (4)
      Mimi Hines
      Billie Holiday (4)
      Jennifer Holliday
      Rosetta Howard (2)
      Helen Humes (5)
      Alberta Hunter
      Betty Hutton
      June Hutton
      Bertha Idaho (2)
      Bessie Jackson
      Fran Jeffries
      Myrtle Jenkins & Bumble Bee Slim
      Edith Johnson (3)
      Ella Johnson (2)
      Lil Johnson
      Margaret Johnson (2)
      Merline Johnson
      Stella Johnson
      Albennie Jones
      Betty Hall Jones (2)
      Etta Jones
      Maggie Jones
      Madeline Kahn
      Laura Kenyon
      King Sisters
      Nora Lee King
      Sara Riva Krieger
      Nancy La Mott
      Frances Langford
      Paula Lawrence
      Julia Lee (3)
      Peggy Lee
      Dorothy Loudon (2)
      Nellie Lutcher
      Sara Martin (2)
      Mary Ann McCall
      Mary McCarthy (2)
      Viola McCoy
      Hattie McDaniel
      Sarah McLawler
      Armelia McQueen
      Danny Meehan (2)
      Memphis Minnie (2)
      Ethel Merman
      Lizzie Miles (2)
      Ann Miller
      Rose Mitchell
      Monette Moore (2)
      Ella Mae Morse
      Helen O'Connell
      Anita O'Day (2)
      Bibi Osterwald
      Edith Piaf
      Billie Pierce
      Charlotte Rae
      Ma Rainey
      John Reardon
      June Richmond
      Isie Ringgold
      Chita Rivera
      Lyda Roberti
      Betty Roche
      Charles Rydell (3)
      Hazel Scott (2)
      Blossom Seeley
      Mark Sendroff
      Dinah Shore
      Ethel Shutta
      Arthur Siegel
      Bessie Smith
      Clara Smith (2)
      Mamie Smith (2)
      Trixie Smith (2)
      O'Neil Spencer
      Addie "Sweet Peas" Spivey (5)
      Victoria Spivey (5)
      Jo Stafford
      Maureen Stapleton
      Kay Starr (2)
      Jo Sullivan
      Gloria Swanson
      Rosetta Tharpe (2)
      Hociel Thomas
      Big Mama Thornton
      Martha Tilton
      Henrietta Valor
      Sarah Vaughan
      Sippie Wallace (3)
      Dinah Washington
      Ethel Waters (2)
      Mae West (2)
      Georgia White (2)
      Margaret Whiting (3)
      Addie Williams
      Gussie Williams
      Joe Williams
      Cy Young
  - Subseries 3: LP records: British Music Hall and Revue - Solo or Small Revue
    - Coward - Lillie (Box 100)
      - Noel Coward
        The Noel Coward Album, double album, ca. 1965, Columbia MG 30038
        Noel Coward & Gertrude Lawrence, We Were Dancing: songs from Tonight at 8:30 and Private Lives. Also: Gertrude Lawrence with Douglas Fairbanks, Jr. in Moonlight Is Silver; Monmouth Evergreen MES 7042.
        Noel & Gertie & Bea, EMI Parlophone PMC 7135: Noel Coward, Gertrude Lawrence, & Beatrice Lillie
      - Joyce Grenfell
        Joyce Grenfell, The New Collection (double album), 1978, EMI DUO 128
        Joyce Grenfell Requests the Pleasure, mid-1970s, DRG SL-5186
        George - Don't Do That: Six Nursery School Sketches, 1977, EMI Starline, SRS-5199
      - Gracie Fields
        The Gracie Fields Story (double album), mid-1970s, EMI DUO 120
        The Golden Years of Gracie Fields, 1975, WarwickWW-5007
        Amazing Gracie Fields, 1976 reissue of 1930s records, Monmouth Evergreen MES-7079
        The World of Gracie Fields, 1970, Decca Records SPA-82
      - Stanley Holloway
        The Original Stanley Holloway (music-hall numbers), EMI Starline MRS-5104
      - Elsa Lanchester
        Elsa Lanchester: More Bawdy Cockney Songs, vol. 2, Tradition Everest Records 2091
      - Beatrice Lillie
        Queen Bea: a Musical Autobiography (double album), 1979, DRG DARC-2-1101
        Thirty Minutes with Beatrice Lillie (10 inch LP), Liberty Music Shops, LMS-1002 A-B
        An Evening with Beatrice Lillie, 1955, London Records LL1373
        Beatrice Lillie Sings, 1965, JJC M-3003
  - Subseries 4: LP records: British Music Hall and Variety - Compilation Albums
    - Music Hall to Variety - Revue 1919-1929 (Box 100)
      - Music Hall to Variety: volume 2: First House, World Record Club WRC SH-149
        Billy Bennett
        Nora Blaney & Gwen Farrer
        Douglas Byng
        Tom Clare
        Mr. Flotsam & Mr. Jetsam
        Tommy Handley
        Will Hay
        Layton & Johnstone
        Lily Morris
        Charles Penrose
        Leslie Sarony
        Harry Tate
        Sophie Tucker
      - Music Hall to Variety: volume 3, Second House, World Record Club WRC SH-150
        Crazy Gang: Flanagan & Allen, Nervo & Knox, Naughton & Gold
        Florence Desmond
        Gracie Fields
        Ronald Frankau
        Stanley Holloway
        Horace Kenney
        Max Miller
        Tessie O'Shea
        Nellie Wallace
        Elsie & Doris Waters
        Western Brothers
        Robb Wilton
      - Palace of Varieties, London Records LL-297
        Helen Clare
        Rob Currie
        Billie Howard
        Raymond Newell
        Paddy O'Neil
      - Noel Coward: The Revues, EMI: SHB 44
        Noel Coward
        Alysia Delysia
        Maisie Gay
        Doris Hare
      - British Tribute to Stage & Screen Royalty, Magna ZZ89
        Gertrude Lawrence
        Beatrice Lillie
        Nigel Bruce, Cedric Hardwick & C. Aubrey Smith
        Basil Rathbone & Vivien Leigh
        Brian Aherne
        Greer Garson
        Dennis King
      - Nostalgia Trip to the Stars 1920s - 1950s, volume 2, Monmouth Evergreen LP MES 7031
        Elsa Lanchester
        Stanley Laurel & Oliver Hardy
        Ben Lyon & Bebe Daniels
        Adolphe Menjou
        Anna Neagle
        Lili Palmer
        Walter Pidgeon
        Harry Richman
      - (British) Revue 1912-1918, EMI Parlophone: PMC 7145
        Nat D. Ayer & Louise Leigh
        Frank Carter & Isabell D'Armond
        Maurice Chevalier
        Fay Compton
        Teddy Girard
        Robert Hale & Ida Crisp
        Lew Hearne & Bonita
        Elsie Janis & Basil Hallam
        Nelson Keys
        Gerald Kirby
        Gertrude Lawrence & Walter Williams
        Ethel Levey
        Gertie Millar & A. Simon-Girard
        Unity More
        George Robey & Violet Loraine
        Lee White & Clay Smith
      - (British) Revue 1919-1929, EMI Parlophone: PMC 7150
        Edythe Baker
        Joyce Barbour
        Jack Buchanon & Trix Sisters
        Cicely Courtneidge
        Melvin Gideon
        Alfred Lester
        Jessie Matthews & Henry Lytton
        George Metaxa
        Herbert Mundin
        Jack Smith
        Leo White
  - Subseries 5: LP Records: Vaudeville and Early Film Musicals Singers - Compilations
    - Show Biz - Those Wonderful 1930s (Box 100)
      - Show Biz: Vaude to Video, RCA LOC 1011
        Gene Austin
        Ben Bernie
        Fanny Brice
        Cab Calloway
        Eddie Cantor
        Enrico Caruso
        George M. Cohan
        Bing Crosby
        Morton Downey
        Jimmy Durante
        George Gershwin
        Happiness Boys ( Billy Jones & Ernie Hare)
        Hildegarde
        George Jessel
        Harry Lauder
        Helen Morgan
        Will Rogers
        Kate Smith
        Joe Smith & Charlie Dale
        Arthur Tracy
        Rudy Vallee
        Paul Whiteman and others
      - A Night at the Palace, Take Two, TT108
        Seven Little Foys
        Harry Fox
        Irene Franklin
        Willie & Eugene Howard
        Eddie Peabody
        Georgie Price
        Blossom Seeley & Benny Fields
        Van & Schenck
      - Old Curiosity Shop, reissued ca. 1950-51, RCA LPT 1112
        John Barrymore
        Nora Bayes & Jack Norworth
        Marlene Dietrich
        De Wolf Hopper
        Helen Kane
      - Original Musical Comedy 1909 - 1935, RCA LPV 560
        Edith Day
        Gallagher & Shean
        Louise Groody & Charles King
        Libby Holman
        Elsie Janis
        Al Jolson
        J. Harold Murray
        Cole Porter
        Eleanor Powell
        Blanche Ring
        Noble Sissle & Eubie Blake
      - Camp, Capitol Records T 2474
        Harry Belafonte
        Sammy Davis
        Nick Lucas
        Keely Smith
        Glen Gray, Horace Heidt and Harry James and their orchestras
      - Great Stars of Vaudeville, Columbia LP CSS 1509 (2 copies)
        Victor Borge
        George Burns & Gracie Allen
        Clayton, Jackson & Durante
        W.C. Fields
        Baby Rose Marie
      - Those Wonderful 1930s, volume 1, Decca DEA 7-1
        Louis Armstrong
        Kenny Baker
        Bobby Breen
        Deanna Durbin
        Bob Hope & Shirley Ross
        Dorothy Lamour
        Tony Martin
        James Melton
        Grace Moore
        Dick Powell
        Wini Shaw
        Mae West
        Pinky Tomlin
      - Those Wonderful 1930s, volume 2, Decca DEA 7-2 (2 copies)
        Frances Faye
        Benny Fields
        Walter Huston
        Joe E. Lewis
        Ted Lewis
        Mary Martin
        Borrah Minevich & His Harmonica Rascals
        Bill Robinson
        Ethel Waters
      - Those Wonderful 1930s, volume 3, Decca DEA 7-3
        Ben Bernice
        Boswell Sisters
        Arthur Godfrey
        Mills Brothers
        Several dance & swing bands
  - Subseries 6: LP Records: American Vaudeville Performers - Comedians Solo or Duo
    - Bergen - Wynn (Box 101)
      Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy (Show), radio, 1952, Radiola, MR-1034
      Burns & Allen radio show, Radiola Records, MR-1028
      George Burns & Gracie Allen, radio show, Vol. 1, Garabedian Mark 56, #614 (2 copies)
      A Musical Trip with George Burns, 1972, Buddah Records, BDS-5127
      A Date with Eddie Cantor, Carnegie Hall Concert, 1962, Audio Fidelity AFLP 702
      W. C. Fields, Temperance Lecture, 10 inch LP, 2001, Jay Records
      W. C. Fields & Mae West, Fields' monologues, West's songs, Proscenium 22
      Be Frank with Fay, Frank Fay (songs & patter), Bally Hi-Fi, BAL 12015
      Mickey Katz: Star of Broadway's Borschtcapades, 10 inch LP, Capitol Records H-298
      Bert Lahr Radio Broadcasts, 1977, Garabedian Mark 56, #729
      Laurel & Hardy; Golden Age of Hollywood Comedy, United Artists UAG-29676
      Frigidaire presents Lum & Abner, volume 1, 1949, Garabedian Mark 56 #605
      Pigmeat Markham: Here Come the Judge, Chess Records, LPS-1523
      Groucho Marx: Hooray for Captain Spaulding, 10 inch LP, 1952, Decca DL-5405
      Harp by Harpo [Marx], 10 inch LP, RCA Victor LPM-27
      Groucho & Chico Marx: When Radio Was King: You Bet Your Life with Groucho; Hollywood Agents with Groucho & Chico, Memorabilia Records, MLP-733
      An Evening with Groucho, 2 LP set, patter & songs/1972 concert, A & M SP-3515
      Marx Brothers radio broadcasts (mostly Groucho), 4 LPs, Murray Hill Records 931680
      Moran & Mack (side 1); Smith & Dale (side 2); unknown label except "TBCSD 1247"
      Mae West, Original Voice Tracks from Her Greatest Movies, Decca DL-79176
      Bert Williams, patter songs, 1978 reissue, Sunbeam Records P-506
      Ed Wynn: The Fire Chief, 1930s radio broadcasts, Garabedian Mark 56, #621
      Ed Wynn, Grampa Magic at Coney Island, Riverside/Wonderland RLP-1416
  - Subseries 7: LP Records: American Vaudeville Performers - Singers Solo or Duo
    - Brice - Seeley (Box 101)
      Fanny Brice Sings the Songs She Made Famous, Audio Fidelity Records AFKLP-707
      John W. Bubbles Back on Broadway, 1980, Uptown Records UP 27.03
      Bubbles, John W That Is.. ., mid-1960s, Vee-Jay Records VJ-1109
      Al Jolson 1885-1950, Epitaph Records/VJ International E-4008
      The Best of Spike Jones (& His City Slickers) RCA ANL-1035e
      Ted Lewis, Me and My Shadow, Olympic Records 7127
      Helen Morgan Sings, reissue by Audio Rarities 2330
      Rare Originals by Fanny Brice (side 1) and Helen Morgan (side 2) RCA Victor LPV-561
      Club Richman (Harry Richman/Eddie Cantor/Helen Kane), New Torrington Records 432
      Blossom Seeley & Benny Fields, Mr. & Mrs. Show Business, 10 inch LP made in 1952 by Loew's/MGM-E92 to coincide with release of biopic Somebody Loves Me
      Vaudeville Songs of the Great Ladies of the Musical Stage, sung by Joan Morris (William Bolcom/piano), 1976, Nonesuch Records H-71330
  - Subseries 8: LP Records: American Vaudeville Performers - Compilations
    - Those Wonderful Girls of Stage, Screen and Radio, 1930 (one title) (Box 102)
      - Those Wonderful Girls of Stage, Screen & Radio, 1930s, 2 LPs, Epic Records BSN-159
        Irene Dunne
        Ruth Etting
        Alice Faye
        Ella Logan
        Gertrude Niessen
        Martha Raye
        Kay Thompson
        Lee Wiley
  - Subseries 9: LP Records: Broadway Musicals
    - At Home Abroad - Ziegfeld Follies of 1911 (Box 102)
      At Home Abroad (1935), archival reconstruction by Smithsonian, RCA DPM1-0491, lyrics by Howard Dietz & music by Arthur Schwartz. Original cast: Beatrice Lillie, Ethel Waters, Eleanor Powell and Reginald Gardiner; recreations by Cicely Courtneidge, Clifford David, Nancy Dussault and Karen Morrow
      Lew Leslie's Blackbirds of 1928, lyrics by Dorothy Fields, music by Jimmy McHugh (recorded 1932 with original cast members Adelaide Hall and Bill Robinson, and 1930s recreations by Ethel Waters, Cab Calloway, Mills Brothers, Duke Ellington & His Orchestra, Don Redman & His Orchestra), reissued 1968, Columbia Records OL-6770
      Julius Monk's Plaza Nine Revue: Dime a Dozen with Susan Browning, Jack Fletcher, Gerry Matthews, Rex Robbins, Fredericka Weber, Marie Louise Wilson and pianists Carl Norman, William Roy and Robert Colston, 1963, Cadence Records CLP-25063
      Ken Murray's Blackouts, reissued 1975 by Garabedian Mark 59 Records #701
      Gilbert & Sullivan Selections: HMS Pinafore and The Mikado by The D'Oyly Carte Opera Company, London Records SPC-21010
      The Nervous Set, Original Broadway revue cast, Columbia Records OL-5430
      Jerry Herman's Parade, revue with Dody Goodman & Charles Nelson Reilly, Kapp Records 7005
      Ziegfeld Follies of 1919 with Eddie Cantor, John Steel, Van & Schenck and Bert Williams, 1977 reissue by Smithsonian Institution, Columbia Records R-009 / P14272
  - Subseries 10: LP Records: Hollywood Musicals
    - Golden Age of the Hollywood Musical - The Kay Thompson Reviews (Box 102)
      Presenting the Golden Age of the Hollywood Musical (reissue w/pop-up cover 1974) with selections from Gold Diggers of 1933, Gold Diggers of 1935, 42nd Street, Dames and Footlight Parade, with George Raft, Dick Powell, Ruby Keeler, Joan Blondell, James Cagney and Wini Shaw, United Artists Records UAG-2942 (2 copies)